Guide to the Stephen Tennant Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- 1 August 2011 acquisition, 1925-1967; 0.42; (1 boxes)
  - Letter concerning the book "Twenty-five years" - typed copies, 1925 October-December (Box 14)
  - Equestrian and circus sketches (Box 14)
  - Two portrait sketches, woodcut of flower vase, photograph of cricket championship plaque (Box 14)
  - Manuscript writings with pen drawings (Box 14)
  - Letter to Stephen Sperder - miscellaneous manuscript pages (Box 14)
  - Poems, typescript and manuscript (Box 14)
  - "The Kestrel," "Tolerance," in envelope to Miss Lewis (Box 14)
  - Various writings, drawings, and letters to Miss Lewis, 1930s-1950s (Box 14)
  - Stephen Tennant gallery programs, 1950s (Box 14)
  - "Notes," typescripts with comments added to margins (Box 14)
  - Pen drawing of woman by a window (Box 14)
  - Unfinished pen drawing of woman with headdress (Box 14)
  - Pen and watercolor study of people smoking (Box 14)
  - "Fashions - Stage dresses" - pen/watercolor (Box 14)
  - Two pen drawings - 17th/18th century people (Box 14)
  - Gallery invitation, announcement - Pen/marker (Box 14)